[Music]
This is a demonstration of the print viz
co-pilot assisted scheduling
functionality.
Here on the print viz planning board, I
will click the co-pilot icon and
optimize.
I'm going to select the group of
machines I would like to schedule,
the date I want to start the scheduling,
and the end date where I want to finish
scheduling. This time we provide some
optimization options. So these are
reasons why different print shops want
to place certain jobs on one machine as
opposed to another. I will go ahead and
select paper item number and I am going
to say avoid paper changes. Clicking
optimize sends the information to
co-pilot so it can generate a optimize
schedule across these three machines
that we're sending right now. Here it
was able to plan everything that we
sent. So I can go ahead and click load
simulation which loads our planning
board with an optimized schedule across
these three machines based off of the
paper item number and avoiding paper
changes on each of the presses.